

# **Mugia Miftahul Choir**

Address: Cicadas, Sagalaherang, Subang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia, 41282, Subang, Indonesia

Email address: <a href="mailto:mugia.miftahul@gmail.com">mugia.miftahul@gmail.com</a>

**Phone number:** (+62) 83816355113 **Website:** <a href="https://mugia.herokuapp.com/">https://mugia.herokuapp.com/</a>

Website: <a href="https://github.com/mugiachoir">https://github.com/mugiachoir</a>
Whatsapp Messenger: +62 83816355113

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mugia-choir-3b593a1b4/

(i) Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/mugiadesign/">https://www.instagram.com/mugiadesign/</a>

**Date of birth:** 18/06/2001 **Nationality:** Indonesian

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a university student at Universitas Komputer Indonesia majoring in information systems. I have an interest in Web Development and 3D design. I've gained experience working on a different scale of projects, from individual projects to corporate class projects. Yet I still have great determination in learning new stuff.

I also have experience of working with people from different countries and cultures such as British, so I can communicate well with others and am capable of working alone or inside a team.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

[ 06/2020 - 02/2021 ] **Web developer** 

MTs Al-Hidayah Sagalaherang

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

Main activities and responsibilities:

I held all of the jobs in the web development process by myself, including: doing a brief with the client, sketching, wireframing, prototyping, creating high fidelity UI design, designing and implementing a database, front-end, and back-end job

[ 04/2020 - 06/2021 ] **Web developer** 

SMAN 1 Jalancagak Scout Organization

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

Main activities and responsibilities:

My responsibilities were designing the UI of the website, developing the website according to the design, designing and implementing a database, giving the required training for the users, and maintaining the website after it was online

[ 02/11/2019 - 03/11/2019 ] **Graphic designer** 

**Mamah Coet Restaurant** 

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

## Main activities and responsibilities:

I was only tasked to design a banner for their new opening restaurant, so i started by collecting the assets, choosing the art direction, fonts style, and colors because they didn't have an established brand style to follow yet

# [29/11/2020] Graphic designer

### Mamah Coet Restaurant

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

### Main activities and responsibilities:

They came to me to create a simpler version of their logo for some urgent business, so I only have a day to finish the job. What I did was taking a few hours of brainstorming to simplify their logo, aligning my idea with the client, creating a prototype and handing it to them, then doing some revisions

[ 03/09/2021 - 10/02/2022 ] **3D artist** 

### **RFIDiom Ltd**

City: Liverpool

Country: United Kingdom

## Main activities and responsibilities:

I was a part of the Marketing Team at RFIDiom Ltd; my main activities were creating graphics content for social media, or blog. But I also contributed to Branding a few of the company's products. And designing UI/UX of a product website.

My special responsibilities were to create 3D assets and create 3D animations; usually, they were used to demo or advertise products.

On occasions I was also responsible for quality assurance on some websites, looking for errors, bugs, etc.

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[ 30/06/2021 - 03/07/2021 ] Digital Marketing and Graphic Design Training

PT Inovasi Telematika Nusantara VirtualTraining.id

[ 30/12/2020 - 15/02/2021 ] Web & Mobille Design Training

**Zero to Mastery** zerotomastery.io

[ 03/11/2020 - 27/12/2020 ] **React.js Training** 

**Zero to Mastery** zerotomastery.io

[ 10/06/2020 - 29/06/2020 ] Fundamental Front-End Web Development Training

**Dicoding** dicoding.com

[ 17/06/2021 - 08/09/2021 ] **3D Modeling Training** 

**GameDev.tv** gamedev.tv

# [ 14/09/2021 - 27/09/2021 ] **3D Character Creator for Video Games Training**

**GameDev.tv** gamedev.tv

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Indonesian

Other language(s):

# **English**

LISTENING C1 READING B2 WRITING B2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

# **My Digital Skills**

### Design

Adobe Photoshop | Corel Draw | React - React Native | Adobe Illustrator | Figma

# **Programming**

React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript | HTML5/CSS3, SASS, JavaScript (including recent versions)

### 3D

Blender, 3D modeling | 3D animation